2space.net 2012-11-22

# 2SPACE.NET === INFO - PRIVACY POLICY ===

Home » Info : Privacy Policy  |   
---|---  
  
## Info : Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy covers the 2Space® treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your site for inclusion in our database or register as a 2Space® (Passport) Member .   
Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the 2Space® web site, nor does it extend to people that 2Space® does not employ or manage.

### Information Collecting and Use 

The personal information we collect is primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services, and generally this information is not shared with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected, if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that the law requires such disclosure or other special cases described below.

### Registration & 2SPACE® Passport 

2Space® (Passport) Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including e.g. name, address, telephone number. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). 2Space® does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. 

However, in instances where 2Space® and a partner jointly promote the Services, 2Space® may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, the partner may not use personal information for any other purpose. 

2Space® may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. 2Space® may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

### Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to 2Space® staff. 

2Space® does not store any credit card information, as all transactions are processed by PayPal or Ogone.

### Special Cases

It is 2Space®'s policy not to use or share personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, 2Space® may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect 2Space® and our Members.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

2Space® may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions concerning our privacy policy please don't hesitate to contact us.
